2010 YEAR, YOIDO, SEOUL
Are you long?
No, as always.
I spoke with Choo Woon.
He will take you
if everything goes well today.
i will be back
Brother
Are you nervous?
Hello, Kyoto.
Enough.
Well done.
He is coming here.
WITHOUT MERCY
Well, because!
What the hell?
Devil. Damn bastards.
Agov.
Do you even know who you contacted?
Untie me.
Immediately!
Ahoy!
Where is Mr. Gu?
Call Mr. Gu! I will talk to him!
OK!
I will double the amount of money
that Gu Jun Mo promised you.
Double!
Do you know what "double" means?
How funny.
That's exactly what Mr. Gu said, word for word.
I also work for Bonsan!
How long has it been since we've seen each other?
You were just talking about a meeting.
Many years.
Let's sit down.
Heard what happened to that manager, Cha?
It was Jun Mo.
My son did it.
Peven, you know
about his reputation in the company.
Cha seems to have interfered in Jun Mo's affairs.
And Jun Mo hired someone
to get revenge on him
but they went too far.
Those foreigners that Jun Mo brought
take care of them please.
why are you asking me This is your company.
This is a family affair, not a company affair.
He is not sinless, but he is my son.
If I humiliate him,
what will people think
Anyway, why are you asking me?
This is your family.
For this I offer help
in your question with the land plot.
I, Gu Bong Sun,
ready to take a loss-making deal.
- Ah!
- We are leaving!
Yes exactly!
Take care of Goo Bong San's case.
Sir, these are Bonsan Group problems.
your truth
But Gi Suk
he will decide for that
our problem with the plot in Yoido.
So now that's our problem.
NAM GI SOK
DIRECTOR OF CHUVUN GROUP
Why don't you ask Choi Song Chol?
what are you
are you serious
I said so. After me, you are next.
Why do you suddenly want to leave the company?
Gi Soku, this is your business.
And all this will come in handy,
when you will manage the company.
I checked what you requested.
Gu Jun Mo's reputation
in "Bonsan" nowhere.
So much so that he had to
hire people from abroad.
CHEON HYE BOM
"CHUVUN"
Are you all right?
And what? Looks like no?
No, sir.
Sorry.
Hey Bom.
What do you want to do when you quit?
Sorry?
I'm much better off without this Cha.
DE'CRO HOTEL
Agov, Okure.
Well done.
Sir, here comes Nam Gi Seok…
Everything is fine.
Let him come in.
You have three days.
Fly to the homeland.
It seems you caused trouble there too,
but it is not safer here.
Better go from here.
What kind of cholera?
Director Name.
Why is the person from Chuvun here?
I'm asking you. What did you forget here?
Mr. Gu personally asked Mr. Li.
Because he is such a successful businessman
ready to suffer losses for his son
and step over your own pride.
GU JUNG MO, DIRECTOR OF BONSAN
Mr. Director.
If you don't know how, it's better not to do it.
It will be better for you, sir.
"If you don't know how, don't do it"?
Well, what...
As a director, you have the right to say so.
Your brother did it, didn't he?
So how now...
his leg
What is Gi Seok doing there?
Excuse me?
Ah, what about Gi Seok?
went to Gu now?
Yes, that's why he came.
grandfather
You shouldn't have let him go, jerks!
Ten years have passed?
Oh, and they made a mess then.
It would be better if he did everything your way then.
Unfortunately, he didn't listen. Like me now.
Then my father and Mr. Lee Choo Woon
managed to clean up the mess after him.
But he was left alive.
Only the Achilles tendon was cut.
And his brother is still living off Chu Wong.
How inconvenient.
Mr. Name.
Am I doing the right thing or not...
what to you What are the problems?
What...
you
You are the problem.
Agov.
Nam Gi Suk!
You just crossed the line!
How cold
Fits well.
Won't you ask?
What?
"How are you doing?"
"Do you have a girlfriend?" Ordinary things.
We haven't seen each other in six years.
The director wants me to…
headed "Zhuvun" after him.
Doesn't that make you happy?
I don't know if it's really good.
Maybe I should work here too?
I have to go now.
is everything ok
I thought you wouldn't ask.
CHUVUN COMPANY
CORPORATE GALLERY
Get out already.
why do you always come
Of course, because you have nowhere to go.
Who sent you?
You're gone, bastard!
Cattle.
Is this Gu Jun Mo?
Is it Director Gu himself?
Although I think that you do not know.
get up
Ahoy!
Bastard!
Are you waiting for an invitation? Beat him!
Okay, follow him!
Scumbag!
Dovben
Yes.
CHUVUN
"BAEKCHONG CONSTRUCTION"
TO OUR KOREAN PARTNERS
What a tragedy.
I still…
had a lot to learn from him.
My condolences.
Treat the directors with respect.
do you know something
What?
About what?
About Mr. Nam.
CHWE SONG CHOL
MANAGER, "CHUVUN"
Isn't that you?
How can you say that?
Mr. manager.
Gi Seok was my friend.
Friendship is more important than anything.
Including for "Chuvun".
Well, of course he was a friend.
You have betrayed your friends more than once.
First you were one of us.
Do newbies know about it?
Father, the police...
They say it was some minors.
Don't make an elephant out of a fly.
So you really are hiding something.
Not worth it
talk to me like that now.
Prosecutor Lee.
Have you left work before?
Where is Mr. Nam's memorial hall?
They must be tired.
Maybe you will go home to rest?
Take him away.
ELDEST SON OF LEE JU WUN
LEE HYUM SONG
Is this visit a business one for you?
Mr. President of the company is there.
And what?
You know what he wants.
He wants you to
did not participate in the company's affairs.
It is only for you
attending the farewell ceremony,
but for my people
everything will not end so quickly.
I will talk to my father.
Please guide me.
Song Cheol.
This is Mr. Nam's brother.
Pay him respect.
where is he
Gi Seok.
Who did it?
As I said, he got it
in a fight with young homeless people...
Song Cheol.
Is that all? Really?
So what are you going to do?
Nam Gi Seok is gone now.
Look for another successor.
Don't be so stubborn, give Geum Sung a chance.
This is a good opportunity to support my son.
What is good about it?
do you think that
what happened to gi seok - is it good?
Well, because
I'm not talking about that.
Gi Seok did not deserve to die like this.
CHUVUN
Gi Joon.
what are you doing here
You said to live as if I were already dead.
But today I can't do that.
Sorry.
OK. I understand that
given the circumstances.
Of course you must visit
his brother's funeral.
Remember the agreement 11 years ago?
Of course, I remember.
You promised that we would not see you.
Not that one.
There was one more.
I promised I wouldn't let
for Gi Seok to suffer.
I kept my word
but you didn't keep yours.
- Gi Jun.
- Gi Seok's death...
Is there anything else I should know?
What?
Nothing, no?
I'll take it as no.
Gi Jun.
Sir! Gee Jun!
are you leaving already?
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Jeong Hye Bum. I was Gi Seok's subordinate.
I will make sure that…
Gi Seok was duly honored.
CAMPING AS A BUSINESS
CAMPING
NAM GI JUN
CAMPING "CHONGSIN"
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, GI JUN!
FROM GI JUICE
I'm sorry.
Relatives of victims are not allowed to visit him,
because he is suspected of a serious crime.
I'm only for a little while.
Those are the rules.
I am very sorry.
Well, you heard.
I understand everything, but the investigation is ongoing.
He is a suspect, but not yet proven guilty.
I understand. I only
I ask permission to see him.
Why do you need it?
It's against the rules.
You're not even his relative.
You are a relative of the victim.
So when the trial begins,
then you will see him whether you want it or not.
It's probably easier to live
becoming just an investigator.
What?
Since when did you start...
play by the rules?
come in
What the hell?
What were you doing there for so long?
Do we know each other?
You didn't just go to smoke.
Why did you go there?
You think you can just
come here and sneak around?
who are you
Who ordered you to kill my brother?
You are his relative.
forgive me
Excuse me!
You wanted that, right? You're a fucking asshole.
I wonder why I killed him?
What do you think?
He looked at me the same way
how are you right now
I'll find your friends first -
all to one,
who was with you that day
And after that...
i will find your family
always
do me a favor
When you find my fucking parents
blow them away from me properly.
No, but better...
just kill them.
Those creatures abandoned me
with a little brother and disappeared.
So find them and kill them.
Clear.
You have a younger brother.
Bus number 476 is expected to arrive.
Don't stop!
To the right.
- Hell.
- San Yone.
Is this your first time here? Sit where you want.
No, on the right.
- Come in.
- I'm going, Min Soo.
Ahead!
Devil.
I told you, I'm digging.
Time to go guys.
- Did you hear what I said?
- Well, everyone leave.
You have a good instinct.
I said he would come.
Get out of here, you bastards.
- Class, Yoo Cheol!
- Everyone leave!
You're a damn talented actor.
Hey, lock the door.
- Can I go?
- Scared?
Watch and learn, kid.
don't touch me
- Agov.
- Go crazy, how cute.
Hey, old man!
I heard you went to Yu Chang
and got excited, right?
Well, try the same with us.
Well, because
Do it you scumbag.
Is that all?
You didn't bring me here.
I brought you here.
- What a slipper you are.
- How scary.
Speak up.
Who sent you?
But no one sent us.
Look how strict.
We killed him, okay?
Or what? Finish you too?
Just say so.
Anu say
Badge!
Whore!
What are you waiting for? Come on!
Bastard!
Slutty bitch!
sorry
Oh, beat him!
Ahead!
Ahead! Badge!
What to do?
Open the door!
Faster, bitch!
We don't know who it was.
Yes?
You wanted to do it!
- Hell, for sure!
- No, it was Yu Chan!
Sir, it wasn't me. I swear
Please believe me.
sir
Please...
WITHOUT MERCY
Let's go, we have to run.
- We have to go.
- Faster!
Go all!
Away!
Let's run away!
Let's run!
Translation of subtitles: Olga Tsiatska